<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Gun_Pecheneg.label>PKM</Gun_Pecheneg.label>
  <Gun_Pecheneg.description>The light machine gun, despite its high weight and low accuracy, has found its use in the Zone. It is used mainly to fight superior opponents or to clear mutant lairs.</Gun_Pecheneg.description>
  <Gun_Pecheneg.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Pecheneg.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Pecheneg.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Pecheneg.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_PKM.label>PKM bullet</Bullet_PKM.label>

  <Gun_SVU.label>SVU</Gun_SVU.label>
  <Gun_SVU.description>A more modern version of the SVDm-2 sniper rifle, which uses a bullpup layout to reduce its dimensions. It has a higher rate of fire compared to its "parent" with a smaller weight, while the accuracy of combat at short and medium ranges remains approximately the same. Today it enjoys well-deserved popularity in the troops and among stalkers.</Gun_SVU.description>
  <Gun_SVU.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_SVU.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_SVU.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_SVU.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_SVU.label>SVU bullet</Bullet_SVU.label>

  <Gun_SVD.label>SVD</Gun_SVD.label>
  <Gun_SVD.description>It was widely used in all combat operations conducted by the Soviet army since the early 1960s. It proved itself to be an exceptionally reliable and easy-to-use weapon.</Gun_SVD.description>
  <Gun_SVD.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_SVD.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_SVD.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_SVD.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_SVD.label>SVD bullet</Bullet_SVD.label>

  <Gun_Mark.label>Mark I EMR</Gun_Mark.label>
  <Gun_Mark.description>An American-made semi-automatic rifle introduced in the early 1950s, it has undergone several modernizations and upgrades over the years..</Gun_Mark.description>
  <Gun_Mark.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Mark.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Mark.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Mark.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Mark.label>Mark bullet</Bullet_Mark.label>

  <Gun_RPG7u.label>RPG-7u</Gun_RPG7u.label>
  <Gun_RPG7u.description>A grenade launcher from the 1960s, which remained in huge quantities in army warehouses, from where it ended up in the Zone. It is a smooth-bore, single-shot, recoilless launcher equipped with a PGO-7 optical sight with a magnification of 2.7 diopters. Its impressive dimensions and heavy weight make this weapon not very common among stalkers, but due to its enormous destructive power and ease of use, it has found loyal admirers in the Zone.</Gun_RPG7u.description>
  <Gun_RPG7u.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_RPG7u.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_RPG7u.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_RPG7u.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_RPG.label>RPG launcher shell</Bullet_RPG.label>

  <Gun_M701A.label>M701 Super</Gun_M701A.label>
  <Gun_M701A.description>Bolt-action sniper rifle. Considered a sport weapon on the Mainland, yet rather popular among mutant hunters and stalkers headed for Prypiat.</Gun_M701A.description>
  <Gun_M701A.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_M701A.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_M701A.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_M701A.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_M701A.label>M701 bullet</Bullet_M701A.label>

  <Gun_Gaussrifle.label>Item 62</Gun_Gaussrifle.label>
  <Gun_Gaussrifle.description>A super-precise weapon assembled by designers in the Zone. It works almost silently, since energy sources are used for filming, not gunpowder gases. Despite the colossal power of the shot, the Gauss gun has very little recoil. In terms of accuracy and lethal force, it surpasses any classic small arms.</Gun_Gaussrifle.description>
  <Gun_Gaussrifle.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Gaussrifle.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Gaussrifle.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Gaussrifle.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Gauss.label>Gauss bullet</Bullet_Gauss.label>

  <Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.label>Serial gauss gun</Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.label>
  <Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.description>Product 62, which has undergone major changes. Parts of the artifacts built into the power coils allowed the projectile to accelerate to higher speeds, which had a positive effect on accuracy. Due to the increase in the power of the coils, the charging time of the capacitors was also increased. On the wooden butt is visible the inscription, "Trust no one, except the monolith and your brothers, no one ..."</Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.description>
  <Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Gaussrifle_HUNTER.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_HUNTER.label>HUNTER bullet</Bullet_HUNTER.label>

  <Gun_Bulldog-6A.label>Bulldog-6</Gun_Bulldog-6A.label>
  <Gun_Bulldog-6A.description>A revolver-type grenade launcher. Sometimes simply irreplaceable, in particular when clearing large areas of mutants, attacking guarded stationary objects, in combat with particularly tenacious creatures..</Gun_Bulldog-6A.description>
  <Gun_Bulldog-6A.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Bulldog-6A.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Bulldog-6A.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Bulldog-6A.tools.1.label>


  <!--<Bullet_Bulldog.label>Bulldog launcher shell</Bullet_Bulldog.label>-->

</LanguageData>