<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <!-- Industrial -->

  <Gun_PTM.label>PTM</Gun_PTM.label>
  <Gun_PTM.description>The most common pistol in the zone is a legacy of the Soviet era. Quite reliable and cheap, it has a low magazine capacity with insufficient power and unsatisfactory cartridge accuracy. The main weapon of a novice stalker.</Gun_PTM.description>
  <Gun_PTM.tools.0.label>grip</Gun_PTM.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_PTM.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_PTM.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_PTM.label>PTM bullet</Bullet_PTM.label>

  <Gun_Viper.label>Viper-5</Gun_Viper.label>
  <Gun_Viper.description>This submachine gun has a proven track record of reliability, ease of use, and high accuracy. Adopted by many countries' military and police forces, it has appeared on the black market and eventually made its way to the Zone.</Gun_Viper.description>
  <Gun_Viper.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Viper.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Viper.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Viper.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Viper.label>Viper bullet</Bullet_Viper.label>

  <Gun_M10Gordon.label>M10 Gordon</Gun_M10Gordon.label>
  <Gun_M10Gordon.description>Low price and low precision – that’s all you need to know about this submachine gun. Especially popular among rookies, but not for long. Real Zone life soon shows just how risky it is to cheap out on gear.</Gun_M10Gordon.description>
  <Gun_M10Gordon.tools.0.label>grip</Gun_M10Gordon.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_M10Gordon.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_M10Gordon.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_M10Gordon.label>M10 Gordon bullet</Bullet_M10Gordon.label>

  <Gun_Buket.label>Buket S-2</Gun_Buket.label>
  <Gun_Buket.description>The Buket S-2 is a versatile weapon for close and even medium range firefights. With it's low fire rate and recoil it is easy to manage while firing it in full-auto. The Buket S-2 uses 9x18mm which is one of the most common and cheapest ammo types found in The Zone. Combined with the armor-piercing variant of the 9x18mm the Buket S-2 can take out armored opponents with ease. The Buket's biggest weakness it's low magazine capacity of 20 rounds + 1 in the chamber. Obtaining the high capacity attachment is a must for the Buket which boosts it's magazine capacity to 30 rounds. It is also relatively cheap (compared to other primary weapons) to repair and upgrade the Buket. The Buket S-2 can be a good companion-piece for a Stalker looking for close range engagements or someone who is looking for a solid backup weapon.</Gun_Buket.description>
  <Gun_Buket.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Buket.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Buket.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Buket.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Buket.label>Buket bullet</Bullet_Buket.label>

  <Gun_Colt.label>Rhino</Gun_Colt.label>
  <Gun_Colt.description>Originally used as an African buffalo hunting pistol, the Rhino is a supremely powerful revolver that will blow enemies away from close-to-mid range and is especially effective against radioactive mutants.The power of the Rhino is such that it even rivals some shotguns, but it doesn't compromise on accuracy or range, making it the best overall sidearm in terms of raw power. The only real drawback is its limited ammo capacity and loudness, which can alert nearby enemies quite often.</Gun_Colt.description>
  <Gun_Colt.tools.0.label>grip</Gun_Colt.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Colt.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Colt.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Colt.label>Colt bullet</Bullet_Colt.label>

  <Gun_IntegralA.label>Integral-A</Gun_IntegralA.label>
  <Gun_IntegralA.description>An elite submachine gun renowned for its effectiveness in confined spaces. A favorite among seasoned diggers.</Gun_IntegralA.description>
  <Gun_IntegralA.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_IntegralA.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_IntegralA.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_IntegralA.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_IntegralA.label>IntegralA bullet</Bullet_IntegralA.label>

  <Gun_Zubr.label>Zubr-19</Gun_Zubr.label>
  <Gun_Zubr.description>The Zubr-19 is a submachine gun  The weapon has the following statistics: 50 round magazine by default Very high rate of fire Abundant 9x19 ammunition type .</Gun_Zubr.description>
  <Gun_Zubr.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Zubr.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Zubr.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Zubr.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Zubr.label>Zubr bullet</Bullet_Zubr.label>

  <Gun_FNFive.label>FN Five-seven</Gun_FNFive.label>
  <Gun_FNFive.description>FN Five-seven is in service with the elite mercenaries who work in the north of the zone. It is highly valued by stalkers, but if the mercenaries catch you with this gun, they will kill you on the spot.</Gun_FNFive.description>
  <Gun_FNFive.tools.0.label>grip</Gun_FNFive.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_FNFive.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_FNFive.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_FNF.label>FNF bullet</Bullet_FNF.label>


</LanguageData>