<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Gun_Groza.label>Grom S-14</Gun_Groza.label>
  <Gun_Groza.description>Automatic rifle and grenade launcher system – an assault rifle configuration that can come in quite handy in the Zone. A good fit for lovers of ultimate firepower at both short and medium distances.</Gun_Groza.description>
  <Gun_Groza.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Groza.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Groza.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Groza.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Groza.label>Groza rifle bullet</Bullet_Groza.label>


  <!-- UnderBarrel Bullet -->

  <STLKR_UBLGrenade.label>grenade</STLKR_UBLGrenade.label>

  <Gun_AKM74M.label>AKM-74</Gun_AKM74M.label>
  <Gun_AKM74M.description>A folding machine gun, model 1974, chambered for 5.45 × 39. It is a simple and reliable weapon, although the low cost of production has somewhat affected the ease of use and accuracy of combat. In the Zone, this is the main weapon of the military, stalkers, and many loners.</Gun_AKM74M.description>
  <Gun_AKM74M.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_AKM74M.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_AKM74M.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_AKM74M.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_AK.label>AK  bullet</Bullet_AK.label>

  <Gun_Dnipro.label>Dnipro</Gun_Dnipro.label>
  <Gun_Dnipro.description>The perfect assault rifle for 5.45x39 cartridges. Excellent damage and high armor-piercing percentage are the key to success. Yes, it is expensive to maintain, but it deserves it. The best machine gun, after which you can forget about balance problems and inflated health of monsters.</Gun_Dnipro.description>
  <Gun_Dnipro.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Dnipro.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Dnipro.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Dnipro.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Dnipro.label>Dnipro bullet</Bullet_Dnipro.label>

  <Gun_AKSU.label>AKSU</Gun_AKSU.label>
  <Gun_AKSU.description>In terms of dimensions and weight, it is close to submachine guns, but the mechanism is almost completely identical to the AKM-74/2. The small dimensions of the weapon allow it to be successfully used in urban areas and in cramped conditions, and the bullet's penetrating power is quite high. Among the disadvantages are a short sighting range and a tendency to quickly overheat.</Gun_AKSU.description>
  <Gun_AKSU.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_AKSU.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_AKSU.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_AKSU.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_AKSU.label>AKSU bullet</Bullet_AKSU.label>

  <Gun_Fora.label>Fora-221</Gun_Fora.label>
  <Gun_Fora.description>This modular next-gen assault rifle has earned multiple prestigious global accolades, along with unofficial commendations from the stalker community.</Gun_Fora.description>
  <Gun_Fora.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Fora.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Fora.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Fora.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Fora.label>Fora bullet</Bullet_Fora.label>

  <Gun_FNF2000G.label>FN F2000G</Gun_FNF2000G.label>
  <Gun_FNF2000G.description>Automatic rifle and grenade launcher system – an assault rifle configuration that can come in quite handy in the Zone. A good fit for lovers of ultimate firepower at both short and medium distancesThis is a futuristic type of weapon - a serially changing automatic grenade launcher complex of modular design. It is equipped with a 40-mm grenade launcher and a computerized sight-fire control module. Despite its external bulkiness, it is highly ergonomic, easy to control fire in all modes and highly reliable.</Gun_FNF2000G.description>
  <Gun_FNF2000G.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_FNF2000G.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_FNF2000G.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_FNF2000G.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_FNF2000G.label>FN F2000 rifle bullet</Bullet_FNF2000G.label>

  <Gun_IL86A.label>IL-86</Gun_IL86A.label>
  <Gun_IL86A.description>The shortcomings of this rifle discovered during operation led to the fact that most of the weapons were modernized, and the written-off batches ended up in the Zone through the black market. The main advantages are the standard four-power optical sight, high accuracy of a single shot and high potential for modernization. When firing in bursts, the accuracy of the battle drops sharply, and the automation shows a tendency to delay.</Gun_IL86A.description>
  <Gun_IL86A.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_IL86A.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_IL86A.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_IL86A.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_IL86A.label>IL86  bullet</Bullet_IL86A.label>

  <Gun_Vintar.label>SSR</Gun_Vintar.label>
  <Gun_Vintar.description>"Special Sniper Rifle" is designed for silent and flameless sniper shooting during special operations when it is necessary to keep the shooter's position secret. Its ammunition provides high armor-piercing and stopping effects; in addition, this weapon is equipped with an integrated silencer and optics. Despite the small-capacity magazine, it is highly valued by stalkers.</Gun_Vintar.description>
  <Gun_Vintar.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Vintar.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Vintar.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Vintar.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Vintar.label>SSR bullet</Bullet_Vintar.label>

  <Gun_VAL.label>VAL</Gun_VAL.label>
  <Gun_VAL.description>It is based on the silent sniper rifle "Vintar-VS", from which it differs in a folding stock, standard ability to fire in bursts, and a more capacious magazine. It was originally intended for use by special forces in conditions requiring silent and flameless shooting.</Gun_VAL.description>
  <Gun_VAL.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_VAL.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_VAL.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_VAL.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_VAL.label>VAL bullet</Bullet_VAL.label>

  <Gun_GP37A.label>GP-37</Gun_GP37A.label>
  <Gun_GP37A.description>The embodiment of new trends in Western-made automatic weapons: the principle of operation of the automatic system is based not on a semi-free bolt, but on a short stroke of the gas piston. It must be said that the changes have clearly been beneficial: this assault rifle is a first-class example of a modern weapon - light, reliable and ergonomic.</Gun_GP37A.description>
  <Gun_GP37A.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_GP37A.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_GP37A.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_GP37A.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_GP37A.label>GP37  bullet</Bullet_GP37A.label>

  <Gun_Trc301A.label>Trc-301</Gun_Trc301A.label>
  <Gun_Trc301A.description>A lightweight rifle with an effective firing range of up to 300 meters. Thanks to the exceptionally smooth trigger, high ergonomics and light weight, this weapon is characterized by high accuracy of fire, although its high sensitivity to contamination makes it not always suitable for use in difficult field conditions.</Gun_Trc301A.description>
  <Gun_Trc301A.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Trc301A.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Trc301A.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Trc301A.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_Trc301A.label>Trc-301  bullet</Bullet_Trc301A.label>

  <Gun_SGI.label>SGI</Gun_SGI.label>
  <Gun_SGI.description>A representative of a relatively new family of assault rifles. Due to its high reliability, accuracy in combat and ease of use, it is one of the best examples of weapons of this class. It is rarely encountered in the Zone and costs a lot of money; usually, it is specially ordered for themselves by experienced stalkers.</Gun_SGI.description>
  <Gun_SGI.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_SGI.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_SGI.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_SGI.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_SGI.label>SGI  bullet</Bullet_SGI.label>

  <Gun_HK416A.label>HK-416</Gun_HK416A.label>
  <Gun_HK416A.description>The successor to the M4 and M16, created by the German company "Heckler and Koch". It stands out for its greater reliability and resistance to dirt.German quality. Made with a clear conscience.</Gun_HK416A.description>
  <Gun_HK416A.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_HK416A.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_HK416A.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_HK416A.tools.1.label>

  <Bullet_HK416A.label>HK416  bullet</Bullet_HK416A.label>

  <Gun_Abakan.label>AC-96/2</Gun_Abakan.label>
  <Gun_Abakan.description>The weapon of the elite troops in the Russian army. It was designed as a replacement for the outdated Akm 74/2. Not only the Obokan's internal mechanisms but also its receiver and its barrel are movable, which decreases the recoil and increases accuracy.</Gun_Abakan.description>
  <Gun_Abakan.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Abakan.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Abakan.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Abakan.tools.1.label>


</LanguageData>