<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>

  <Gun_OBREZ.label>Boomstick</Gun_OBREZ.label>
  <Gun_OBREZ.description>This small and lightweight sawed-off hunting shotgun proved itself surprisingly useful in the ever-changing environment of the Zone. Very efficient in close quarters and comfortable for concealed carry.</Gun_OBREZ.description>
  <Gun_OBREZ.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_OBREZ.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_OBREZ.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_OBREZ.tools.1.label>

  <Gun_TOZ34L.label>TOZ-34</Gun_TOZ34L.label>
  <Gun_TOZ34L.description>A common hunting rifle, widespread and cheap. Still beats a handgun when it comes to dealing with mutants.</Gun_TOZ34L.description>
  <Gun_TOZ34L.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_TOZ34L.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_TOZ34L.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_TOZ34L.tools.1.label>

  <Gun_M860n.label>M860 Cracker</Gun_M860n.label>
  <Gun_M860n.description>"A pump-action shotgun prized for its lightweight build and reliability, it has earned a distinguished reputation as one of the world's most famous shotguns and remains extremely popular in the Zone."</Gun_M860n.description>
  <Gun_M860n.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_M860n.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_M860n.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_M860n.tools.1.label>

  <Gun_TOZBM16M.label>TOZ BM-16</Gun_TOZBM16M.label>
  <Gun_TOZBM16M.description>TOZ BM-16 is an excellent weapon for hunting small animals: wild boars, cats, blind dogs. Quite accurate and at the same time with good indicators of killing power and stopping power. That's all, the obvious advantages end there. The double-barreled shotgun takes quite a long time to reload, and two charges are clearly not enough. So it is not worth going with this weapon to people or some chimeras..</Gun_TOZBM16M.description>
  <Gun_TOZBM16M.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_TOZBM16M.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_TOZBM16M.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_TOZBM16M.tools.1.label>

  <Gun_Otboynic.label>Otboynic</Gun_Otboynic.label>
  <Gun_Otboynic.description>A smoothbore combat shotgun designed to increase the firepower of special forces of the army and police. The main advantages are a high magazine capacity and a practical rate of fire; Disadvantages are the significant dimensions and weight of the weapon, as well as the low speed of the main reload. Zones are rare and are used mainly for clearing mutant magazines.</Gun_Otboynic.description>
  <Gun_Otboynic.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Otboynic.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Otboynic.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Otboynic.tools.1.label>

  <Gun_SPSA.label>SPSA-12</Gun_SPSA.label>
  <Gun_SPSA.description>A special-purpose smoothbore automatic shotgun with the ability to switch between firing modes. Developed in the second half of the 20th century, it continues to be used as a universal combat weapon for police and army assault units. It is highly reliable and tactically flexible. Despite its large mass, complex design, and high price, it is quite popular in the Zone as an effective means of combating mutants..</Gun_SPSA.description>
  <Gun_SPSA.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_SPSA.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_SPSA.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_SPSA.tools.1.label>

  <Gun_Saiga.label>Saiga-12k</Gun_Saiga.label>
  <Gun_Saiga.description>The Saiga-12K "Taktika" smoothbore semi-automatic shotgun variant - the shotgun has a wooden fore-end and pistol grip, a left-folding tubular buttstock like the "SVD-S". The standard sighting devices include a front sight and a rear sight like the "AK". The ammunition is fed from special detachable box magazines of various capacities (in this variant, the magazine holds 8 rounds).</Gun_Saiga.description>
  <Gun_Saiga.tools.0.label>stock</Gun_Saiga.tools.0.label>
  <Gun_Saiga.tools.1.label>barrel</Gun_Saiga.tools.1.label>


</LanguageData>